{
  "questions": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "prompt": "What special prop should always be included for lists of elements?",
      "answers": [
        "id",
        "name",
        "key",
        "prop"
      ],
      "correctIndex": 2
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "prompt": "A React component is a function that returns ______.",
      "answers": [
        "HTML",
        "JSX",
        "props",
        "state"
      ],
      "correctIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "prompt": "Which event handler will run when a user is finished filling out a form?",
      "answers": [
        "onSubmit",
        "onClick",
        "onChange",
        "onForm"
      ],
      "correctIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "prompt": "______ is a tool that transpiles JSX into valid JavaScript.",
      "answers": [
        "React",
        "Babel",
        "Webpack",
        "ES6"
      ],
      "correctIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "prompt": "What syntax makes it possible to unpack values from arrays, or properties from objects, into distinct variables?",
      "answers": [
        "spread",
        "key-value",
        "coalescing",
        "destructuring"
      ],
      "correctIndex": 3
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "prompt": "Returning different elements from a component depending on the state of your application is known as _____ rendering.",
      "answers": [
        "voodoo",
        "conditional",
        "reactive",
        "controlled"
      ],
      "correctIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "prompt": "What is jsx?",
      "answer1": "Javascript syntax extension for react",
      "answer2": "Html used in react",
      "answer3": "Javascript code",
      "answer4": "Css code to style react components",
      "correctIndex": 0,
      "id": 7
    },
    {
      "prompt": "What is jaba?",
      "answer1": "Kaveve",
      "answer2": "Ndom",
      "answer3": "Ngwai",
      "answer4": "fegi",
      "correctIndex": 0,
      "id": 8
    },
    {
      "prompt": "akldhj;ikadadldkal",
      "answer1": "assxaaxads",
      "answer2": "adadadadassdd",
      "answer3": "fweeasfs",
      "answer4": "adsasas",
      "correctIndex": 0,
      "id": 9
    },
    {
      "prompt": "akldhj;ikadadldkal",
      "answer1": "assxaaxads",
      "answer2": "adadadadassdd",
      "answer3": "fweeasfs",
      "answer4": "adsasas",
      "correctIndex": 0,
      "id": 10
    },
    {
      "prompt": "akldhj;ikadadldkal",
      "answer1": "assxaaxads",
      "answer2": "adadadadassdd",
      "answer3": "fweeasfs",
      "answer4": "adsasas",
      "correctIndex": 0,
      "id": 11
    },
    {
      "prompt": "akldhj;ikadadldkal",
      "answer1": "assxaaxads",
      "answer2": "adadadadassdd",
      "answer3": "fweeasfs",
      "answer4": "adsasas",
      "correctIndex": 0,
      "id": 12
    },
    {
      "prompt": "8777gjhjjlkkl",
      "answer1": "kck;ckkck'ld",
      "answer2": "kxklz;z;z;z",
      "answer3": "kcdkkdlks",
      "answer4": "kdskldkldslks",
      "correctIndex": 0,
      "id": 13
    }
  ]
}